Edson Costa

Porto Alegre, Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil



edtech1985@gmail.com



(+55) 51992002595



linkedin.com/in/criptoinvestidor85

Summary

Bachelor in Business Administration with a degree in Foreign Trade. During the course I did internships in some sectors such as logistics, administrative and financial.

At the end of 2021 I decided to start my career transition from financial to the Tech area.

From that moment on, I started studying at Alura with Logic, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and currently PHP. I recently started the Harvard CS50x course - Introduction to Computer Science, especially to improve my technical english.

I am currently working as a Technical Support Analyst L2 at Lit Onlearning - Saint Paul Educacional.

During college I did a 2 year exchange to New Zealand where I reached fluency in the English language. Advanced Spanish. Previous job as a Bilingual Compliance Ombudsman (English and Spanish).

Investor in the traditional financial market(stock markets) since 2015. Investor and enthusiast in the crypto market since 2016.

Soft Skills:

Great interpersonal relationship; Team work; Fast learning; Ease with logic and numbers; Multitasking; Communication; Proactivity; Desire to learn; Autonomy; Owner thought; Focus on quality; Flexibility and ability to adapt to change

Hard Skills:

Blockchain, Excel, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL and MongoDB

Experience



Technical Support Analyst

LIT Onlearning

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Answering tickets via HelpDesk system with SLA, performing tests, creation of spreadsheets and reports, make corrective and preventive maintenance, queries and updates in database (SQL and MongoDB), charging customers via Postman, writing manuals of procedures for knowledge base/FAQ and analysis and handling of tickets through the JIRA.

🔉 Compliance Ombudsman - Bilingual

Contato Seguro | Canal de Ética

Nov 2015 - Jun 2019 (3 years 8 months)

Bilingual Compliance Ombudsman (English and Spanish). Compliance service to customers, suppliers and employees of the contracting companies.

Manager

Costa & Marchiori

Jun 2013 - Jun 2015 (2 years 1 month)

General administration, negotiation with suppliers, accounts payable and receivable, bank reconciliation, purchases, sales, etc.

Billing Analyst

Lommez Assessoria Contabil Fiscal

Aug 2014 - Jan 2015 (6 months)

Credit analysis, refunds, returns and exchanges. Release of data of legal processes.

Service provided within the company headquarters of Dell Technologies Brazil.

Hertz Fleet Assistant

Hertz

Mar 2011 - Mar 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Logistics, data entry system, maintenance logistics, contact with workshops, financial support, accounts payable and receivable, bank reconciliation, management support, fines entry, operational support, delivery and inspection of vehicles.



Construction Assistant

0800 Labour

Jan 2007 - Jan 2008 (1 year 1 month)

General services in construction.

M Customer Service Attendant

McDonald's

May 2007 - Jul 2007 (3 months)

Clerk / Cashier / Runner

Education



Estácio

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, International Business/Trade/Commerce Mar 2003 - Dec 2012



Harvard University

Bachelor's degree, CS50X - Introduction to Computer Science

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

Introduction to the intellectual enterprises of computer science and the art of programming. This course teaches students how to think algorithmically and solve problems efficiently. Topics include abstraction, algorithms, data structures, encapsulation, resource management, security, software engineering, and web programming. Languages include C, Python, and SQL plus HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Problem sets inspired by the arts, humanities, social sciences, and sciences. Course culminates in a

final project. Designed for concentrators and non-concentrators alike, with or without prior programming experience. Two thirds of CS50 students have never taken CS before. Among the overarching goals of this course are to inspire students to explore unfamiliar waters, without fear of failure, create an intensive, shared experience, accessible to all students, and build community among students.

Licenses & Certifications

- JavaScript: primeiros passos com a linguagem Alura f8412c7d-b007-414e-9e8a-b87b1342d2e3
- JavaScript: Programando a Orientação a Objetos Alura a96ce0d8-1f45-4ed6-98a9-20d3e9e89a07
- a HTTP: Entendendo a web por baixo dos panos Alura
- Algoritmos e Lógica de Programação 2022 O Curso COMPLETO Udemy UC-b394332f-cf8e-49c2-852f-0f8776c62703/
- 3 SQL SERVER: Introdução ao SQL com Microsoft SQL Server 2019 Alura 511fc40a-7109-4c63-a1d8-c5bf8297db87
- AULA ON-LINE SOBRE O QUE É A TECNOLOGIA BLOCKCHAIN? LIT
 Onlearning
 a94200b8c0239853f53129f9053fa402
- Pensamento Computacional DIO CC40A289
- Hour of Code Basics concepts of Computer Science Code.org
 _1_99a2f530fad601e86d8bf768ccb4e130
- Lógica de Programação Essencial DIO C0E95A50
- Introdução ao Git e ao GitHub DIO 299A18D0
- Projetos ágeis com SCRUM DIO
 A309239A
- Criando seu Primeiro Repositório no GitHub Para Compartilhar Seu Progresso DIO

DB181DB9

die.	Primeiros passos	para desenvolvimento web -	DIO
	4B57C59E		

- Introdução a criação de websites com HTML5 e CSS3 DIO 6495FA50
- Construindo páginas para internet com Bootstrap DIO 1641FCD2
- Recriando a Interface do Netflix DIO 91175948
- Coleções DIO 82AFFCB9
- Debugging e Error Handling DIO 5D994B00
- Javascript Assíncrono DIO 6CE368E8
- JS Orientação a Objetos DIO 2793D4DB
- Introdução ao ReactJS DIO D79D0079
- Manipulando a D.O.M. com JavaScript DIO
 A9D790BE
- Desenvolvimento de aplicações para internet com ReactJS DIO 6AEACDC5
- HTML5 E CSS3 PARTE 2: POSICIONAMENTO, LISTAS E NAVEGAÇÃO Alura 46d36d71-4654-40fd-a6fa-502d4b49d85c
- HTML5 E CSS3 PARTE 3: TRABALHANDO COM FORMULÁRIOS E TABELAS Alura

1 LÓGICA DE PROGRAMAÇÃO II PRATIQUE COM DESENHOS, ANIMAÇÕES E UM JOGO - Alura

e37c1b3a-3c07-40db-b93b-f0ae0482f4bf

- HTML5 E CSS3 PARTE 4: AVANÇANDO NO CSS Alura 894f391d-286a-4a14-adb1-42c5cec6fb04
- **JAVASCRIPT: OBJETOS** Alura 35791079-5828-4796-b52b-00a96bd8e603
- JAVASCRIPT: PROGRAMAÇÃO ORIENTADA A OBJETOS Alura 86c2e880-b0a8-43e4-bee8-b43ded4b5e20
- JAVASCRIPT: TIPOS, VARIÁVEIS E FUNÇÕES Alura 09bca8c8-f43b-4c00-a1e4-83ce346525e5
- **EF SET Certificate** EF Standard English Test (EF SET) uom12W
- ARQUITETURA DE COMPUTADORES: POR TRÁS DE COMO SEU PROGRAMA FUNCIONA Alura c669034c-6322-43b1-9f4e-cc88acb23c7f
- JAVASCRIPT E HTML: DESENVOLVA UM JOGO E PRATIQUE LÓGICA DE PROGRAMAÇÃO Alura

ed800a70-8fea-400e-8391-faa546aa7e62

- 2 LINUX I: CONHECENDO E UTILIZANDO O TERMINAL Alura 9717d248-f696-4387-bf0c-eab276ffff91
- **JAVASCRIPT: ARRAYS** Alura 8fe17f03-8591-4b60-8e65-5400d914b2ad
- JAVASCRIPT: OBJETOS Alura c312a66c-6035-42b0-a448-d44b813878ef
- **AVANÇANDO COM PHP: ARRAYS, STRINGS** Alura f7f00b13-66dc-492c-95e0-20098d898080

- PHP Conceitos, lidando com dados, loops e mais Alura 4abe1b1d-df3e-40b6-b826-71188a18d16a
- Curso Microsoft SQL Server 2022 Conhecendo o SQL Alura 322bc667-a832-46f0-b0e8-bf0f620890be
- ORM COM NODEJS: API COM SEQUELIZE E MYSQL Alura
- REACT: DESENVOLVENDO COM JAVASCRIPT Alura
- React Crie sua primeira página web Alura 589b00d0-e59e-4801-adc9-ebea2226f077
- Microsoft SQL Server 2022 Consultas avançadas Alura a0eae7b3-367e-43d9-98dc-97edaf1b5b5d
- REACT: LIDANDO COM ARQUIVOS ESTÁTICOS Alura 6d62e11a-6644-4ead-b751-28e41bd23790
- **EF SET Certificate** EF Standard English Test (EF SET) uom12W
- React Conhecendo a biblioteca React Router Alura 4bd3f124-e7a2-4e7b-97d4-3ee95c169286

Skills

React.js • Google Sheets • Technical Analysis • PHP • Account Reconciliation • Databases • Teamwork • Microsoft Office • Customer Service • Technical Support